4.11.2023 23:40 Right Resume



Anil OZTURK

Civil Engineer & General Management M.Sc. Student

About Me

I am Anil Ozturk and I have 7 years of experience in infrastructure projects and 5 years of experiences in planning, progress monitoring, risk management, cost control. I have worked as a project controller in the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia and Iraq in an EPC contractor and worked as a construction supervisor in Turkey.

In my last project I worked as a planning engineer in an oil production facility in Iraq. The contract value was 80M USD and the client was Exxon. I was in charge of preparing Level-4 schedules, following up on actual progress and notify delays to the top management in advance.

I can speak advanced English and fluent Turkish (C1) and German as an intermediate level (B1).

The importance of soft skills in planning is obvious and I have developed myself in maintaining effective communication, collaboration, adaptability, problem-solving, critical thinking, time management, leadership and conflict resolution throughout the projects.

4.11.2023 23:40 Right Resume

I would enjoy having the opportunity to talk with you to show you the links between my abilities and my earned knowledge with your expectations like:

- Create, monitor and analyze Project/Manufacturing schedules from the beginning of a project. - Monitor Project, workflow, and schedules to ensure ontime delivery. - Identifying & Tracking critical path. - Determining various approach to bring deviated plan by innovative reports, bottlenecks identifying. - Design Comprehensive dashboard by Power BI assist to understand current situation of Project. - Creating warning points in case of forecasting delays like Engineering tasks or Equipment deliveries. - Ensure that materials and equipment are prearranged for production, Order or shipment to project. - Work with managers to develop potential solutions to improve production performance. - Generate daily or weekly production reports to managers for critical decision-making purposes. - Develop production schedules in accordance with sales forecast, plant, and employee capacity, and new business opportunities. - Forecast Risks and finding mitigation plan by meetings and having Risk Maps. - Integrating Soft skills and Project Management tools to have a smooth work place.

Thank you for your time and attention. I look forward to hearing you.

Age 32

Email anil.oeztuerk@pfh.de

Phone +49-1525-9817524

Address Kreuzbergring 44, Goettingen, Germany

Professional Skills

Primavera

EPC Coordination

Pipelines

Tilos

Microsoft Office

Work Experience

Project Control Engineer at at Renaissance Heavy Industries-Iraq

October, 2019 - April, 2023

-Leading team to guide the importance of work orders, sequences, project material deliveries area-wise at Project Site in accordance with contract milestones. -Resource planning and optimization. - Earned Value Management: CPI, SPI Analysis and escalating deviations to senior project management. -Risk Management: Following-up actual progress and based on the update schedule, escalate the critical path and delays to senior project management.

Project Control Engineer at MAPA Construction and Trade Co.-Kingdom of Saudi Arabia

April, 2018 - October, 2019

Preparation resource loaded baseline after setting up meetings with all stakeholders and monitoring the updates, informing deviations and delays to the project management. -Produced the Weekly Progress Report containing progress summary table, "actual vs planned" S-Curves, look ahead bar chart and other ad-hoc reports. -

4.11.2023 23:40 Right Resume

Earned Value Management: CPI, SPI Analysis and escalating deviations to senior project management.

Construction Supervisor at Punj Lloyd-Limak-Kalyon Joint Venture

December, 2016 - April, 2018

-Supervision of all site works, create equipment and manpower schedule based on available resources.

Education

4.11.2023 23:40

Masters in General Management from Private University of Applied Sciences

2022 - 2023

The Master of Science programme enables to gain the skills and academic depth required to be a successful and responsible manager in an increasingl globalized world.

Bachelor of Civil Engineering from Middle East Technical University-Turkey

2016

With a capability of applying fundamentals of knowledge towards the analysis of complex civil engineering problems and preparing students for a wide and changing spectrum of professional career opportunities.

Science and Mathematics from Izmir Science High School-Turkey

2010

Focusing of fundamental sciences.

Contact

Address

Kreuzbergring 44, Goettingen

Phone

+49-1525-9817524

Email

anil.oeztuerk@pfh.de

★https://twitter.com/templateflip

a

https://www.facebook.com/templateflip

0

https://www.instagram.com/templateflip

https://github.com/templateflip